And today is the fifty-fourth.
Is it raining for a guy,
bro?
ok ok
а,
New castle.
Let it choose there.
Here's a great business idea,
if program halfway through,
rain has a new concept of Mars and I'm going to introduce it to
companies because I'm sure I'll be able to make their business better.
See,
but for that I need to prospect a guy and see if anyone buys my idea.
Are you on?
So I came down an avenue here.
Wish me luck,
bro?
E
Hey guys,
what's your name?
It's the pleasure Caio.
I actually wanted to exchange an idea with the marketing people.
All right,
who's responsible?
Alright, I'm great.
You wanted to know who is responsible for talking
about marketing here you wanted to do it for the store,
for the company.
It's with c.
That I can help you out there,
really man.
I'm going to wait for your contact,
so I'd like to know who is responsible for
the company would like to get the contact.
Then in January,
you get in touch.
Thank you.
Did you see caraca,
bro?
It's squeezing this rain here,
old man.
You know,
when you realize that the person who took care of you,
I think you own it?
Something, man.
And she called the employee to talk to me.
He kept looking at her to ask the questions,
my manager.
But I'll see if she can help you.
Thank you.
You having 1 tea chair here.
Now we arrive full of ideas,
right?
Sometimes the stop doesn't work,
bro.
You look at the place,
you know you have a solution for that place that you can help with ideas
that will improve the business and the person doesn't even listen to you.
Handle
it could be another day lost,
you know,
but no bro,
you won't have the opportunity all the time,
all the time,
you have to create madness,
put your finger there,
hope to work.